Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 69, folder: 17 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Report to the Congress of the United States by the Comptroller General of the United States, Publication (Box 69, Folder 17)
    Febraury 1966. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 18 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Production Bonus Plan for Employees of United States Potash Compnay, Publication (Box 69, Folder 18)
    June 1, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1953 Mine Agreement between United States Potash Company and Carlsbad Potash Basin Union, Independent, Publication (Box 69, Folder 18)
    May 12, 1953. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 19 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Letter to the President, Publication (Box 69, Folder 19)
    October 4, 1962. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 20 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining: A Report by the President's Advisory Committee on Labor-Management Policy, Publication (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Report Setting Forth the Committee's Views on the Guideposts for Noninflationary Wage and Price Behavior, Publication (Box 69, Folder 20)
    August 18, 1966. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 21 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Full Partnership of Women in our Democracy, Publication (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Box: 69, folder: 22 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A Summary of Activities 1964-1967, Publication (Box 69, Folder 22)
- Box: 69, folder: 23 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: This is the President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: This is the President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Booklet About Employment of the Handicapped, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: More Defense Business for Sheltered Workshops: Highlights of a Panel Discussion, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: 15 Years 1947-1962, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: This is the President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: This is the President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: Employment Assistance for the Handicapped: A Directory of Federal and State Programs to Help the Handicapped to Employment, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: Steps to Action: A Program Guide, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Steps to Action: A Program Guide, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
- Box: 69, folder: 24 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: For All Americans Equality in Job Opportunity: The goal of the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Federal Governmnet Employmet Rules and Regulations of the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
    Effective July 22, 1961, Amended February 27, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Government Contract Employment Rules amnd Regulations of the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
    Effective July 22, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Government Contract Employment Rules and Regulations of the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
    Effective July 22, 1961, Amended November 23, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Federal Government Employment Rules and Regulations of the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Equal Employment Opportunity in Federal Government on Federal Contracts, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: The American DreamEqual Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
    May 19, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Implementing Plans for Progress, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
- Box: 69, folder: 25 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 30, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    October 1, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    September 9, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    August 25, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    August 6, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    August 26, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    July 15, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 13: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    August 27, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 23, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 16: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 11, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    May 21, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 20: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    May 18, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    May 4, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    April 30, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    April 29, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    April 5, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    March 18, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    January 13, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    January 8, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Plans for Progress, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    August 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    January 4, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 31: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    December 22, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    October 7, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    September 1, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    September 22, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 36: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 37: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    July 7, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 8, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    July 8, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 41: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    August 14, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 43: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 10, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 29, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    May 17, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    May 28, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 3, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 5, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    April 24, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 51: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    May 1, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    January 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 54: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 55: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 56: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    October 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 58: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    September-October 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 19, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    July 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 62: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    September-October 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    January 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    July-August 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 66: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 67: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 68: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 69: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 70: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 71: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    May 18, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 73: Information from the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
    June 25, 1965. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 26 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Information for Release, Publication (Box 69, Folder 26)
    May 25, 1961. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 27 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Rules and Procedure: A Guide to the Taylor Law, Publication (Box 69, Folder 27)
- Box: 69, folder: 28 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Pattern for Progress: Final Report to President Eisenhower from the Committee on Government Contracts, Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
- Box: 69, folder: 29 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The President's Committee on Migratory Labor: Report of a Meeting held on January 17, 1962, Publication (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Equal Job Opportunity is Good Business, Publication (Box 69, Folder 29)
- Box: 69, folder: 30 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The President's Committee on Youth Employmentour greatest resource, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: The Challenge og Jobless Youth, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: The Challenge of Jobless Youth, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
- Box: 69, folder: 31 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Hearing on Nomination of Frank Carter Squire to be a Member of the Railroad Retirement Board, Publication (Box 69, Folder 31)
    March 11, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: How to Compute Railroad Survivor Benefits, Publication (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: In Brief: Benefitsfor railroad employees and their families, Publication (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Occupational Differences in Separation Rates for Railroad Workers, 1957-1959, Publication (Box 69, Folder 31)
- Box: 69, folder: 32 (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Personnel Policy Manual, Publication (Box 69, Folder 32)
- Box: 69, folder: 33 (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Career Opportunities with United States Rubber Company, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Management Appraisal, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Welcome to Ball-Band!, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: Working with U.S. Rubber, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: 'Old Timer'how he lives and what he thinks, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: You and United States Rubber Company, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: Your Job at Ball-Band, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 8: In Step With Naugatuck Footwear Plant, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 9: Your Tomorrow Begins Today at United States Rubber: Career Opportunities for the College Graduate, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 10: Managerial Position Description Form, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 11: Managerial Position Description Form, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 12: Personal History, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 13: Personal History, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 14: Industrial Relations Department Induction Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
- Box: 69, folder: 34 (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Joilet Sponsors Intensive Program to Explain Benefits, Company Policies, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    May 1, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Round-Up: "U.S." Plant Activities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    December 18, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: All-Out Drives Bring Improved Quality to Footwear Plants, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    March 12, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Have You Planned This Year's "Get Out the Vote" Campaign?, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    May 25, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Round-Up "U.S." Plant Activities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    March 25, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Chicopee Employes Submit 781 Quality Suggestions, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    April 5, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Providence Saves $139, 000 in Three Month Contest, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    October 17, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: U.S. Rubber Exchange Report Form, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Item 9: Improved Safety Publicity is Bringing Results, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    September 26, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: President Humphreys' Outlines Company Stand on "Little League", Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    July 9, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Round-Up: "U.S." Plant Activities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    April 4, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Open House Introduces New Chemical Plant to Employes and Neighbors in Gastonia, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    February 15, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Round-Up: "U.S." Plant Activities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    June 18, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: A Horse That Talks Horse Sense, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Item 15: Display of Competitor Products Sets Theme of Mishawaka's Annual Report Employe Meeting, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    May 16, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: New Literature Available for Plant Community Use, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    June 2, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Round-Up: "U.S." Plant Activities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    October 8, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Round-Up: "U.S." Plant Activities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    June 24, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Dramatic Photo Panel Display Unit Tells Story of Rubber Plantation, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    April 11, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Round-Up: "U.S." Plant Activities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    August 6, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Tire Division Issues Communication Policy, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    June 11, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Community Congratulates Hogansville on Plant's 25th Anniversary, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    January 17, 1957. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 35 (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Press Relations: A Guide to Better Community Relations, Publication (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Your Plant's Community Relations: A Guide to Better Community Relations, Publication (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Your Plant's School and Youth Program: A Guide to Better Community Relations, Publication (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: 68th Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: The Magazine of United States Rubber, Publication (Box 69, Folder 35)
    January-February 1956. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 36 (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: U.S. Rubber Public Relations Programs: Our Company, Publication (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Report to Employees: What You Told Us About Yourselves and Your Jobs with United States Rubber Company, Publication (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: 64th Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Annual Report 1951, Publication (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: The Magazine of United States Rubber, Publication (Box 69, Folder 36)
    January-February 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Script for Our Business Year 1951, Publication (Box 69, Folder 36)
- Box: 69, folder: 37 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Your Plant's Open House Program: A Guide to Better Community Relations, Publication (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Your Plant's Good Neighbor Program: A Guide to Better Community Relations, Publication (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: United States Rubber Quarterly, Publication (Box 69, Folder 37)
    July 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: United States Rubber Quarterly, Publication (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Item 5: News Digest, Publication (Box 69, Folder 37)
    May 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: News Digest, Publication (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Item 7: News Digest, Publication (Box 69, Folder 37)
    June 1961. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 38 (Box 69, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: United States Rubber Company Presents a Suggestion Plan for All Employees of the Gillette Tire Plant, Publication (Box 69, Folder 38)
- Box: 69, folder: 39 (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Product Directory and Fact Book, Publication (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: United States Rubber Company Administrative, Publication (Box 69, Folder 39)
    A[ril 21, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Visit to a Rubber Plantation, Publication (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: Rubber: A Story of Romance and Science, Publication (Box 69, Folder 39)
- Box: 70, folder: 1 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Memorandum to Commission Employees in the Headquarters Office, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
    January 18, 1951. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, folder: 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Work on Securities Exchange Commission, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    August 15, 1957. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, folder: 3 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Letter to Vincent, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    October 22, 1969. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, folder: 4 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Public Statement of Loan Policy: Explanation of Loan Procedures, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    September 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Small Business Administration: What it is, What it Does, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    December 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Small Business Administration: What it is, What is Does, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)